Guide to the Merton H. Miller Papers 1941-2002
University of Chicago Library
- Series III: University of Chicago
  - Subseries 2: Writing and Research
    - "An Approach to the Regulation of Bank Holding Companies" (with Fischer Black and Richard A. Posner), 1978, drafts, notes and correspondence, 1971-1976 (Box 32, Folder 1-7)
    - "An Approach to the Regulation of Bank Holding Companies" (with Fischer Black and Richard A. Posner), 1978, drafts, notes and correspondence, 1971-1976 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - "The Stochastic Properties of Velocity and the Quantity Theory of Money" (with John P. Gould, C. R. Nelson and Charles W. Upton), 1978, drafts and correspondence, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - "Prices for State-Contingent Claims, Some Estimates and Applications" (with Fischer Black and Richard A. Posner), 1978, correspondence, notes and drafts, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 3-5)
    - "Dividends and Taxes" (with Myron S. Scholes), 1978, drafts and notes, 1976-1979 (Box 33, Folder 6-8)
    - "Yield-Tilting, An Appraisal" (with Myron S. Scholes), commissioned by the American National Bank and Trust Company of Chicago, draft, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Talks given to alumni groups, drafts, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Taxes, notes and memorandum, 1978-1979 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Multiperiod variables, notes, ca. 1970s (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Drafts and notes, ca. 1970s (Box 34, Folder 5-7)
    - Reuben A. Kessel, Essays in Applied Price Theory (edited with Ronald H. Coase), 1980, correspondence and drafts, 1978-1979 (Box 34, Folder 8-9)
    - Executive Program graduation address, drafts and programs, 1979-1980 (Box 34, Folder 10-11)
    - "Can Management Use Dividends to Influence the Value of the Firm?" presented at Seminar on Current Management Issues, Bohlins Auditing Bureau, Stockholm, 1981, drafts, correspondence and conference material, 1981-1982 (Box 34, Folder 12-14)
    - "Executive Compensation, Taxes and Incentives" (with Myron S. Scholes), 1982, drafts and notes, 1981-1982 (Box 34, Folder 15-16)
    - "Executive Compensation, Taxes and Incentives" (with Myron S. Scholes), 1982, drafts and research material, 1978-1981 (Box 35, Folder 1-4)
    - "Dividends and Taxes, Some Empirical Evidence" (with Myron S. Scholes), 1982, drafts, notes and research material, 1980-1982 (Box 35, Folder 5-7)
    - "Dividends and Taxes, Some Empirical Evidence" (with Myron S. Scholes), 1982, drafts, notes and correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 36, Folder 1-4)
    - Daniel Feenburg, correspondence and drafts, 1980-1981 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - "Remarks at the Dean's Fund Luncheon," drafts, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 6-7)
    - "The January Anomaly," Woodward Court lecture, drafts, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - "Do Dividends Really Matter?" presented at the Seminar on Current Management Issues, Bohlins Auditing Bureau, Stockholm, drafts, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - "Dividend Policy, Does Generosity Pay?" for presentation at the University of Texas at Dallas, drafts, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - "More on Dividends," presented at the Executive Program Luncheon, drafts, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - "American Management and Management Education, Too Nearsighted or Too Farsighted?" convocation speech, drafts, notes and program material, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 3-5)
    - "A Test of the Hotelling Valuation Principle" (with Charles W. Upton), 1985, drafts, notes and research material, 1980-1983 (Box 37, Folder 6-8)
    - "Behavioral Rationality in Finance, The Case of Dividends," 1986, drafts and correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 38, Folder 1-3)
    - "Economic Costs and Benefits of the Proposed One-Minute Time Bracketing Regulation" (with Sanford J. Grossman), 1986, drafts, research material and correspondence, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 4-9)
    - "Economic Costs and Benefits of the Proposed One-Minute Time Bracketing Regulation" (with Sanford J. Grossman), 1986, draft and correspondence, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 1-2)
    - "Reply to CFTC Staff Comments on the Grossman-Miller Study on the Costs and Benefits of One-Minute Bracketing (with Sanford Grossman), drafts, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Tax policy, research material, 1981-1986 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Macroeconomics, a Neoclassical Introduction (with Charles W. Upton), preface to the paperback edition, 1986, drafts, ca. 1986 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - "Inflation and Capital Markets, Some New Approaches," presented in Abant, Turkey, drafts and correspondence, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Speeches presented in Leuven, Belgium, drafts and correspondence, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Earl M. Combs, Jr., Award presented by the Directors of the Chicago Board of Trade Educational Research Foundation, correspondence and notes, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Frank Milne, correspondence and drafts, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Financial innovation, speeches presented in Belgium, London, Virginia, and Colorado, drafts, research material and correspondence, 1980-1987 (Box 39, Folder 10-12)
    - "The Academic Field of Finance, Some Observations on Its History and Prospects," presented on receiving an honorary doctorate from Katholieke Universiteit, Leuven, Belgium, drafts, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - "Academic Finance, Rewards, Replacements and Renewals," presented on receiving the Scholar's Award of the Eastern Finance Association, draft, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Conference on the Impact of Stock Futures Trading, drafts and conference material, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Speeches, drafts, notes and clippings, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - "The Informational Content of Dividends," 1987, drafts and correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 5-7)
    - "Liquidity and Market Structure" (with Sanford J. Grossman), 1988, drafts, correspondence and research material, 1985-1987 (Box 40, Folder 8-10)
    - "Liquidity and Market Structure" (with Sanford J. Grossman), 1988, drafts, correspondence and research material, 1985-1988 (Box 41, Folder 1-6)
    - "The Modigliani-Miller Propositions after Thirty Years," 1988, drafts, research material and correspondence, 1957-1988 (Box 41, Folder 7-9)
    - "The Modigliani-Miller Propositions after Thirty Years," 1988, drafts, research material and correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 42, Folder 1-3)
    - Conference on Leveraged Buyouts, Chicago Analysts Society, drafts, correspondence and conference material, 1987-1988 (Box 42, Folder 4-5)
    - "Black Monday" stock market decline of October 19, 1987, drafts, conference material and research material, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 6-8)
    - "Black Monday" stock market decline of October 19, 1987, drafts, conference material and research material, 1987-1988 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - "Who Should Set Futures Margins?" presented at the Regulatory Issues in Financial Markets Conference, sponsored by the Chicago Board of Trade, drafts, conference material and research material, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 2-3)
    - 125th Anniversary of the Stockholm Stock Exchange, 1988, drafts, research material and conference material, 1988-1989 (Box 43, Folder 4-7)
    - Conference on Regulatory Reform of Stock and Futures Markets, Columbia University, research material, notes and conference material, 1988-1989 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Speeches given in Sydney, notes, travel material and clipping, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Speech given in Paris, notes and clippings, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Speech given in Maui, notes, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - "The Crash of 1987 and the Crash of 1946," presented at the Conference on Crashes and Panics in Historical Perspective, New York University, draft, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - "The Crash of 1987, Bubble or Fundamental?" presented at the First Annual Pacific Basin Finance Conference, Taipei, drafts, notes and travel material, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 1-2)
    - "Should Short-Term Trading Be Taxed?" drafts and correspondence, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 3-4)
    - "Strategies for Capital Market Structure and Regulation" (with Charles W. Upton), 1989, drafts, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - "Equilibrium Relations between Cash Markets and Futures Markets," presented at the Symposium on Financial Futures and Options, Frankfurt, drafts, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Speech given at New York Stock Exchange-London School of Economics Conference, notes, conference material and research material, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Speech given at DePaul University, notes, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Speech given at Drexel University, notes and conference material,1989 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Leasing, research material, ca. 1980s (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Alumni talks, notes and publication, ca. 1980s (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Drafts, notes and reprints, ca. 1980s-1990s (Box 44, Folder 12-17)
    - United States Senate Committee on Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs, Institutional Investors Hearing, notes, research material and correspondence, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - "Margin Regulation and Stock Market Volatility" (with David Hsieh), 1990, drafts, 1989-1990 (Box 45, Folder 2-3)
    - "Financial Innovation and the Stock Market, an Overview," presented at the Conference on International Financial Markets, Honolulu, drafts, notes and research material, 1989-1990 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - "Strategies for Capital Market Structure and Regulation" (with Charles W. Upton), 1989, drafts and correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 45, Folder 5-6)
    - American Enterprise Institute, research material and conference material, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 7-8)
    - Pacific Basin Finance Conference, Bangkok, conference material, 1989-1990 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - "Invited Comment on Fed's Regulatory Policies," drafts and notes, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Japanese financial markets, research material, 1988-1990 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Congreso de Finanzas, Pontificia Universidad Catolica de Chile, keynote speech, drafts, notes and correspondence, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Market Micro-Structure, New York Stock Exchange, University of Southern California and University of California at Los Angeles, conference material, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - "Leverage," Nobel Prize Lecture, 1990, drafts, notes and program material, 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 6-9)
    - Richard C. Stapleton, drafts and research material, 1967-1991 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Dual-class shares, notes and research material, 1987-1991 (Box 47, Folder 2-3)
    - "Reflexions on Financial Leverage," presented at Katholieke Universiteit, Leuven, Belgium, conference material, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Speech given in Essen, Germany, notes and research material, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Restructuring of debt, notes, research material and conference material, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 6-7)
    - Speech given in Prague, drafts, notes and conference material, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 1-2)
    - Speech given in Spain, notes and research material, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Tokyo stock market, research material, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Alumni talks, drafts, notes and organizational material, ca. 1991 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Alumni book signing, notes and organizational material, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Market manipulation, notes and research material, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Initiativkreis Ruhrgebiet, notes, research material and organizational material, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - George Anders, correspondence, drafts and photocopied article, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Martin Lowy, High Rollers, review, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - "Financial Innovation, Achievements and Prospects," 1992, drafts, research material and conference material, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - "Predictability of SP 500 Indiex Basis Changes, Arbitrage-Induced or Statistical Illusion?" (with Jayaram Muthaswamy and Robert E. Whaley), drafts, notes and research material, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - "Predictability of SP 500 Indiex Basis Changes, Arbitrage-Induced or Statistical Illusion?" (with Jayaram Muthaswamy and Robert E. Whaley), drafts, notes and research material, 1991-1992 (Box 49, Folder 1-3)
    - "Index Arbitrage, Villain or Scapegoat," 1992, drafts and research material, 1991-1992 (Box 49, Folder 4-7)
    - "Index Arbitrage, Villain or Scapegoat," 1992, drafts, research material and conference material, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 1-2)
    - Third Convention of the Mexican Securities Market, drafts and conference material, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Speech given at Harvard University, drafts and notes, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Conference in Madrid, drafts, transcript and correspondence, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Convocation speech, drafts and organizational material, 1983-1992 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - The Role of Journals in Scholarly Communication, Centennial Conference in Memory of George J. Stigler, conference material, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Bankers' Summit, Turin, meeting material, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - International Organisation of Securities Commissions (IOSCO), Annual Conference, notes and conference material, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Asia-Pacific Forex Assembly, Bangkok, notes and conference material, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 11-12)
    - University of Chicago Alumni Association, Centennial Alumni Assembly, notes and program materials, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission, Market 2000 study, correspondence, drafts and photocopied articles, 1987-1992 (Box 51, Folder 2-3)
    - Market Micro-Structure, New York Stock Exchange, University of Southern California and University of California at Los Angeles, notes, conference material and research material, 1991-1992 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - "Risk and Return in Futures, A View from the Chicago School," presented at the Managed Futures Symposium, Chicago Mercantile Exchange, notes and symposium materials, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Chapter Eleven bankruptcy, notes and research material, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - "Black Monday" stock market decline of October 19, 1987, notes, research material and organizational material, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Derivatives, research material, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - "Balance-sheet economics," correspondence and research material, 1991-1992 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Corporate governance, notes and research material, 1990-1992 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Treasury auctions, research material, 1991-1992 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Bank regulation, drafts, notes and research material, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 2-3)
    - Dividends, drafts and research material, 1986-1992 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - "Rejoinder to 'Yes, Discounts on Closed-End Funds Are a Sentiment Index" (with Nai-Fu Chen and Raymond Kan), 1993, drafts, notes and correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 5-6)
    - "Tribute at Service in Remembrance of Walter D. Fackler," drafts, notes and memorial material, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 7-8)
    - "Regulation of Financial Markets," 1993, drafts, research material and conference material, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 9-10)
    - "Are the Discounts on Closed-End Funds a Sentiment Index?" (with Nai-Fu Chen and Raymond Kan), 1993, drafts, 1991-1993 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - "Swaps and Systemic Risk in Interbank Markets," presented at the Banking Structure Conference of the Federal Reserve Bank of Chicago, drafts, notes and conference material, 1992-1993 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - "Is American Corporate Governance Fatally Flawed?" presented at the Second Symposium on Global Financial Markets, University of Michigan, drafts, notes and conference material, 1992-1993 (Box 53, Folder 3-4)
    - "Risk and Return in Futures, A Chicago View," presented at the Ninth Anniversary of Singapore International Monetary Exchange Limited (Simex), drafts, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - "Japanese-American Trade Relations in the Financial Services Industry," presented at the Seminar on Japanese-American Trade Relations, University of Chicago, drafts, conference material and research material, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - "The Transition from Socialism to Capitalism, Vietnam vs. Cambodia," presented in Vienna, drafts and notes, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - "The Role of Futures Markets in the U.S. Economy and the Development of Futures Markets in China," presented at the International Conference on Market Economy and China, Beijing, drafts and notes, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Collaborations with Nai-Fu Chen and Raymond Kan, drafts, correspondence and research material, 1991-1993 (Box 54, Folder 1-2)
    - Speech given at Michigan State University, drafts, ca. 1993 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Speech given at Duke University, drafts and correspondence, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Speech given in Stockholm, drafts and program material, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Speech given at Finance Conference, Taipei, drafts and conference material, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Swiss Options and Financial Futures Exchange (SOFFEX), drafts and organizational material, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Vietnam and Cambodia, drafts, research material and organizational material, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 8-10)
    - Speech given in Venezuela, notes, drafts and organizational material, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Speech given in Turkey, notes and organizational material, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Dual-class catalyst, research material, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Regulation reform, drafts and research material, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - "Black Monday" stock market decline of October 19, 1987, drafts, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Clinton administration economic policy, drafts and research material, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Hybrid instruments, drafts and research material, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - East Asian stock markets, research material, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - For-profit exchanges, newspaper articles, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Enron, notes and research material, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Banking reform, drafts, ca. 1993 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Newspaper articles, 1991-1993 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Mark Nielson, dissertation and CV, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - "Is American Corporate Governance Fatally Flawed?" 1994, drafts, 1993-1994 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - "Functional Regulation," 1994, drafts and research material, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - "Inside Financial Derivatives," 1994, drafts, notes and research material, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 3-5)
    - "Mean Reversion of SP 500 Index Basis Changes, Arbitrage- Induced or Statistical Illusion?" (with Jayaram Muthaswamy and Robert E. Whaley), 1994, correspondence and revisions, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - "Japanese-American Trade Relations, Rambo Takes On Godzilla," presented at the University of California-Santa Barbara, drafts, notes and research material, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - "Japanese-American Trade Relations," presented at Southern Illinois University-Edwardsville, drafts, notes and research material, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - "Do We Really Need More Regulation of Financial Derivatives?" speech presented at a client seminar of Banco de Investimentos Garantia, São Paulo, Brazil, drafts and research material, 1993-1994 (Box 57, Folder 1-3)
    - "Japanese-American Trade Relations," presented at St. John's University, drafts and notes, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - "Derivatives Markets," presented at the Continental Bank Southwest Corporate Finance Weekend, Scottsdale, Arizona, drafts, research material and organizational material, 1993-1994 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - "The New Nikkei 300," presented at the Gathering of the Governing Boards of the International Association of Financial Engineers, New York, drafts and newspaper article, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - "Do the Benefits of Stock Markets in Developing Countries Outweigh their Cost?" keynote address for 21st Century Institute Conference, drafts and conference material, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - "On Some Anomalies in the Theory of Regulation," presented at the Symposium on Financial Market Regulation, Princeton University, drafts and symposium materials, 1992-1994 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Financial Accounting Standards Board, drafts and research material, 1993-1994 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Television appearances, correspondence and preparatory material for interviews, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Speech given at University of Rochester, notes and organizational material, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Derivatives, drafts and research material, 1992-1994 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Speech on interest rates given at Widener University, drafts, research material and organizational material, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - China Financial Weekly, drafts, notes and sample issue, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Speech given in Key Largo, drafts, conference material and research material, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Dual-class catalyst, research material, 1992-1994 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Preparatory material for "Knowledge Exchange" interview, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Speech given in Australia, drafts, notes and organizational material, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Drafts, correspondence and research material, 1986-1994 (Box 58, Folder 10-11)
    - Drafts and reprints, 1976-1994 (Box 59, Folder 1-2)
    - "Response to Christie-Schultz," drafts and notes, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - "Do We Really Need More Regulation of Financial Derivatives?" drafts, research material and conference material, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - "Do the Laws of Economics Apply to Japan?" drafts and research material, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 5-7)
    - "Hedging in the Theory of Corporate Finance, Reply to Mello and Parsons" (with Christopher L. Culp), 1995, drafts and notes, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 1-2)
    - China, drafts, research material and conference material, 1993- 1995 (Box 60, Folder 3-11)
    - Speeches given in Frankfurt, drafts and research material, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Speeches given in Zurich and Frankfurt, drafts, research material and travel material, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Quoting behavior on NASDAQ, research material and notes, 1993- 1995 (Box 61, Folder 2-3)
    - Regulatory reform, research material, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Speech given at Walter D. Fackler Professorship Dinner, notes and program material, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Bankers Trust, drafts and research material, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Banking, research material, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - "The Social Costs of Some Recent Derivatives Disasters," 1995, drafts and notes, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 8-9)
    - "Budget Deficits and Federal Fiscal Equilibrium in the U.S. and Italy," presented at the Fifth Conference on Ethics and Economics, Foligno, Italy, drafts and research material, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - "SEC Antics, How Much Disclosure is Enough?" (with Christopher L. Culp), drafts and research material, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - "The Future of Futures," 1997, drafts, research material and organizational material, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 2-3)
    - "Can China Make It?" presented at the EVA Association Meetings, La Quinta, California, drafts, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Chinese Economists Society, correspondence and research material, 1995-1996 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - China, drafts, notes and research material, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - World Economic Forum, drafts and program material, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Catastrophe insurance and risk management, research material and correspondence, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Flat tax, drafts and research material, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Derivatives lectures, drafts, research material and organizational material, 1995-1996 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Insurance futures, correspondence and research material, 1991- 1996 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Electronic trading, research material and notes, 1992-1996 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Leo Melamed, notes and review of memoirs, 1996 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - NASDAQ, notes, graphs and research material, 1996 (Box 63, Folder 3)